# PETER TANZY

(770) 512-3111 pjtanzy@gmail.com

My career goal currently is to move into a full stack developer position. I have some experience in both front-end and back-end technologies. I have limited experience coding JavaScript with ExtJS, but I have greater experience with other technologies such as D3.js. On the back-end side I have experience with Node.js, primarily with the PowerPoint module PptxGenJS.

The skills and traits that I leverage the most within my position are my strong analytical and problem-solving abilities. I'm also patient and methodical which allows me to persevere when faced with difficult challenges. My best trait is my ability to think outside of the box and see beyond the obvious connection.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**JULY 2017 - PRESENT** 

#### **PROGRAMMER 1, SOLUTIONS CATALYST GROUP**

Implemented D3 Force Directed Graph to represent storage environments.

Implemented Node PptxGenJS powerpoint generator and interfaced the generator with backend and portal URLs to automatically generate audit powerpoints.

Enhanced D3 Force Directed Graph to separate and position nodes based on node type.

**JULY 2016 - JULY 2017** 

### **QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST, SOLUTIONS CATALYST GROUP**

Found and tracked all bugs during development of two applications through Jira.

JAN 2013 - JAN 2015

**GROCERY STOCKER, PUBLIX** 

Found and tracked all bugs during development of two applications through Jira.

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2016

PROGRAMMING CERTIFICATE, SOUTHERN POLYTECHNIC STATE UNIVERSITY

2006 -2012

BACHELOR OF ARTS, GEORGIA COLLEGE AND STATE UNIVERSITY